

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Full-stack development
Layout design
Scrum
Angular
C#
Problem-solving skills
Time management skills
Accuracy and attention to detail
Collaborating with other developers
Source control management
Issue management systems (Jira)

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

CONTACT

P: +36 30 207 5454 E: kismarczirobi@gmail.com Area: Hungary, Szeged

SOCIAL

Linkedin: József Kismarczi

JOZSEF KISMARCZI

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT

My name is József Kismarczi, young full stack developer. My general capabilities in a Full-Stack Development(3 years experience): Implementing web design and development principles to build stable software(C#) Bringing mock-ups to life using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, Angular. Communicating technical issues to the developer team in an understandable manner. Building websites and apps that are responsive and usable. Monitoring website performance and rectifying front-end-related issues. Innovative ideas and proof of concepts according to project requirements. Maintaining an organized workflow using a version management tool (like Git,TFS). Testing to identify bugs and technical issues before and after deploying. Documenting bug reports, tickets, and any code changes(Jira).

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Signal Iduna | 2022 - Now

- Stacks:
 - o C#
 - o Angular

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER NewLine kft. | 2019 - 2022

- Developing professional public trasport schedule system websites
- Stacks:
 - o C#
 - Kendo UI,MVC,Boostrap 4,Gulp,HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery,GIT/TFS,SQL,Web API,Swagger

FRONT END SOFTWARE DEVELOPER
Pc Trade Systems kft. | Jun 2018 - Dec 2018

- Developed Angular websites
- Scrum, Jira ticket management

EDUCATION

FLOW ACADEMY

Software developer | 2018